[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "In the fighting game Skullgirls, which character utilizes a folding chair called the Hurting as a weapon?",
    "correct_answer": "Beowulf",
    "answers": [
      "Beowulf",
      "Big Band",
      "Cerebella",
      "Squigly"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Rocket League is a game which features..",
    "correct_answer": "Cars",
    "answers": [
      "Cars",
      "Helicopters",
      "Planes",
      "Submarines"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Who is the leader of Team Mystic in Pokemon Go?",
    "correct_answer": "Blanche",
    "answers": [
      "Blanche",
      "Candela",
      "Spark",
      "Willow"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Which of the following was NOT a playable character in the game Kingdom Hearts: Birth by Sleep?",
    "correct_answer": "Ignis",
    "answers": [
      "Aqua",
      "Ignis",
      "Terra",
      "Ventus"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What household item make the characters of Steins, Gate travel through time?",
    "correct_answer": "Microwave",
    "answers": [
      "Computer",
      "Microwave",
      "Refrigerator",
      "Televison"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What game was used to advertise Steam?",
    "correct_answer": "Counter-Strike 1.6",
    "answers": [
      "Counter-Strike 1.6",
      "Half-Life",
      "Half-Life 2",
      "Team Fortress"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "In the game Fire Emblem: Shadow Dragon, what is the central protagonist's name?",
    "correct_answer": "Marth",
    "answers": [
      "Eliwood",
      "Marth",
      "Robin",
      "Roy"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What is the name of a popular franchise that includes placing blocks down and surviving in an open world? ",
    "correct_answer": "Minecraft",
    "answers": [
      "Grand Theft Auto V",
      "Minecraft",
      "Roblox",
      "Unturned"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "In Splatoon 2, who are the members of Off The Hook?",
    "correct_answer": "Pearl & Marina",
    "answers": [
      "Callie & Marie",
      "Diamond & Aquamarina",
      "DJ Octavio & Crusty Sean",
      "Pearl & Marina"
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "In the PAYDAY series, who betrayed the PAYDAY gang that got Hoxton arrested?",
    "correct_answer": "Hector",
    "answers": [
      "Hector",
      "The Dentist",
      "The Elephant",
      "Vlad"
    ]
  }
]